says.com 2013-06-06

# SAYS Privacy Policy

SAYS is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes to you when and how SAYS collects uses and discloses your information as a user of our Service. When using our Service, you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

### Contacting us about this policy

**If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, contact us at**

Tel: +603 7731 7583  
Lot 7.08B, Level 7, 1 Tech Park,  
Tanjung Bandar Utama, Bandar Utama 47800,  
Petaling Jaya, Selangor, Malaysia  
Or email us: [helpdesk@says.com](mailto:helpdesk@says.com). 

### Personally identifiable information

When you sign up to SAYS, the site collects and uses specific information in order to provide you with our Service, as follows: 

  * **Information collected upon registration**  
When you sign up on SAYS, you provide non-personally identifiable information such as your username, full name, email address, and password. By default, the username you choose is publicly shown on SAYS, including on your profile page and in search results. You are also given an option to show your full name, if you prefer to. 
  * **Demographic information**  
Personally identifiable information may include your date of birth, gender, race, and city. This is found in your account preferences, and is used for the system to show you age-appropriate content. 
  * **Other optional information**  
Entering your phone number is optional, should you require us to contact you via telephone regarding support requests, account suspension, cashing out, or collecting of prizes won. You may choose to enter your biography, your full name and profile image on your public profile page. 
  * **Profile page**  
The types of information mentioned above which go into the profile page can be removed / changed anytime by editing your Account Preferences page. Remember, your profile page information is PUBLIC, this means businesses, third parties, and search engines may crawl it, cache it, and view it. Enter only information you intend to share with the world. 
  * **Inviting friends**  
You may choose to invite your friends by an invite email that is automatically sent from us to your friends when you provide us with their email addresses. We do not store any of these email addresses in our system. If your friends choose to join the Program as a result of your invite, they will have to manually input the information on their own. 

### Non personally identifiable information

  * **Demographic aggregates**  
Demographic aggregates may be shared with advertising partners to give an idea of the SAYS audience. 
  * **Log Data and Unique Visit Metrics**  
Our servers record information when you use the Program (“Log Data”). Log Data information includes your IP address, browser type, operating system, the referring web page, pages visited, location, and cookie information. We receive Log Data when you interact with our services, such as when you sign in to the website, interact with our email notifications, or visit the website via a SAYS widget on a third-party website. Log Data and unique visit metrics are used by our quality algorithms to prevent generation of 'fake traffic', and ensures sharing activity that honours our [Terms of Use](http://says.com/my/terms) are rightfully rewarded. 

This information is not and never will be linked back to you in any way that makes it possible to identify you. 

### Cookies

We use cookies on the website to 

  * provide a faster and safer experience for our users,
  * ensure authenticity of unique visits used to calculate your earnings.

Usage of our cookies falls into the following categories: 

  * **Authentication**  
These cookies tell the system when you're logged in to the site, so we can show you the content available to you as a signed in user. 
  * **Preference**  
These cookies store your preferences about our site, for you to have a meaningful, personalised experience as a SAYS user, including relevant news content. You may also choose to have your username and password remembered when signing in for a faster sign in process. 
  * **Performance**  
These cookies store information that allow certain features on our site to work faster on your browser, such as allowing pages you have seen to be loaded faster. 
  * **Analytics**  
These cookies provide analytics on how you use our site so we can provide a better user experience for you. Measuring this data will help us to continuously improve our service to you. 
  * **Security**  
These cookies help us to keep our community clean and fair for all users, to prevent fake traffic from being generated and rewarded, to encourage fair use of our services, and to apportion rewards and earnings accurately to users who do not violate our [Terms of Use](http://says.com/my/terms). 

### Third-party cookies

  * **Google Analytics**  
This third-party service is used to help us track the usage metrics of our site. Cookies from Google Analytics may be stored in your browser.  
Their privacy policy is available here: <http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/privacyoverview.html>. 
  * **Intercom**  
This third-party service is used to provide you with real-time customer support. For example, the "Talk to Us" button at the corner of your site is powered by Intercom. Cookies from Intercom may be stored on your browser.  
Their privacy policy is available here: <http://docs.intercom.io/privacy.html>. 
  * **New Relic**  
This third-party service is used to help us monitor server and application performance. Cookies from New Relic may be stored in your browser to track information such as how long it takes to load a page.  
Their privacy policy is available here: <http://newrelic.com/privacy>. 
  * **Typekit by Adobe**  
This third-party service is used to help us render beautiful fonts for you. Cookies from Typekit may be stored in your browser.  
Their privacy policy is available here: <http://www.adobe.com/products/eulas/tou_typekit/>. 
  * **Cookies from external sites**  
By using SAYS to view stories, you may choose to load, or follow links to external websites. Those websites may also store cookies in your browser. 

SAYS will never share any personally identifiable information with these third party service providers. 

### Use and disclosure of the information we receive

All uses of the personal information stated is used only for these reasons: 

  * To build a social environment for you to get to know other users
  * To present demographic aggregates to advertisers whose stories are running on our Program
  * To reach you for customer support and resolve issues
  * To send you informational material related to our Services
  * To apportion rewards and earnings accurately to users who do not violate our [Terms of Use](http://says.com/my/terms)
  * To cash out money to users upon user requests
  * To prevent fraud and to address security issues
  * To show relevant customised news content
  * To increase site performance and speed
  * To test, research and analyse data for service improvement
  * To enforce compliance with our [Terms of Use](http://says.com/my/terms) and applicable laws

### Changes to this policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make a change to this policy that, in sole discretion, is material, we will notify you via email notification. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
